Long,
long
Black velvet, a million lights Floating silent
through the endless night The world below
Asleep and blue I'm holding my breath and
Thinking of you
The signal's given, the turn is made The point of
no return, the price is paid The fragile law
begins to shake A promise that we're bound to
make Here comes the friction, we'll abide Burn
in love with our desire.
Seat of flame, crimson glow. The only way we know
to go. We're coming home. We're damn coming
home.
The pressure builds, the gauges scream This is
the violence of the dream A single tear in the
metal skin Is all it takes to let the outside in
Here comes friction Feel the fire Burning up
without desire A sheet of flame A crimson glow
The only way we know to go We're coming home
Breaking through this atmosphere with you
We're losing control
The edges blur A terror and a beauty
Burning up
Here comes the friction, feel the fire Burning
up with my desire Like a sheet of flame, a crimson
glow The only way we know to go, we're coming home
Breaking through this atmosphere with you
Burning up Fixing, running Coming home